(Raj:)Why?
(Howard:)Well, because I've known you
for ten years
(Howard:)and you've never gone to temple,
(Howard:)you never talked
about believing in God,
(Howard:)and last Diwali I watched you
eat two pounds of sacred cow
(Howard:)at a Brazilian steak house.
(Raj:)Religion is
a very personal thing.
(Raj:)I do go to temple--
I just... I don't talk about it.
(Howard:)Yeah, but you're
a scientist.
(Raj:)So?
(Howard:)So, as a scientist,
you believe the way
(Howard:)to understand the universe
is through facts and evidence,
(Howard:)and now
you're counting
(Howard:)on some blue chick
(Howard:)with a hundred arms to help you?
(Raj:)That is so offensive.
Does everything you know
(Raj:)about Hinduism come
from Indiana Jones?
(Howard:)No. There's also Apu
from The Simpsons.
(Raj:)Well, lots of scientists
believe in God.
(Raj:)Okay? Newton,
uh, Faraday,
(Raj:)uh, Pascal-- all were believers.
(Raj:)Even Einstein was famous
for attacking quantum theory
(Raj:)on the grounds
that "God does not play dice
with the universe."
Well, of course
(Howard:)he believed in God--
he slept with Marilyn Monroe.
(Amy:)Actually
there's no proof of that.